Marvin Leath papers, Inclusive: 1954-1994, undated; Bulk: 1979-1991
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Press, 1979-1990, undated; 7
  - Press Releases and Mailings, 1979-1990; 6
    - Mailings, Postal Patron Mailing, Your Personal Budget Exercise, 1985 April 8 (Box 403, Folder 2)
    - Mailings, Postal Patron Mailing, Your Views, Please, 1979 May 14 (Box 403, Folder 3)
    - Mailings, Special Report Mailing, National Defense ReportDLNATO, 1979 February 2 (Box 403, Folder 4)
    - Mailings, Special Report Mailing, Unready for Crisis, 1981 March 27 (Box 403, Folder 5)
    - Mailings, Special Report Mailing, Who Says There’s No Waste?, 1981 February 20 (Box 403, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Additional Strategic Materials Information, 1981 January 6 (Box 403, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Air Force Academy Candidates, 1980 February 1 (Box 403, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Aircraft Carrier Operations Observation, 1981 October 14 (Box 403, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Americans for Constitutional Action (AFCA) Honors Leath, 1980 September 25 (Box 403, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Another Leath Bill Gets Veterans Affairs (VA) Approval, 1981 June 25 (Box 403, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Anti-Terrorism Sanction Act of 1989 Co-sponsorship, 1989 March 22 (Box 403, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Appointments at U.S. Service Academies, 1985 June 14 (Box 403, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Appointments at U.S. Service Academies, 1986 July 3 (Box 403, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Appointments at U.S. Service Academies, 1987 July 13 (Box 403, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Appointments at U.S. Service Academies, 1988 July 26 (Box 403, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Appointments at U.S. Service Academies, 1989 July 10 (Box 403, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Appropriations for New VA Domiciliary, 1985 July 13 (Box 403, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Armed Services Committee Funds for Fort Hood, 1982 April 28 (Box 403, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Armed Services Committee News Release, 1988 August 9 (Box 403, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Armed Services Subcommittee Hearings Uncover Major Waste, 1982 February 22 (Box 403, Folder 21)
    - Press Release, Army Accepts Land for National Guard Armory, 1989 March 17 (Box 403, Folder 22)
    - Press Release, Army Reductions Opposed, 1980 June 19 (Box 403, Folder 23)
    - Press Release, Army Reversal on Filling Prescriptions, 1988 March 30 (Box 403, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, Balanced Budget Statement, 1982 July 16 (Box 403, Folder 25)
    - Press Release, Bertram City Park Funds, 1979 February 19 (Box 403, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, Bill to Award Medal of Honor to Doris Miller, 1989 April 28 (Box 403, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Bill to Help Retirees Under 62, 1983 June 24 (Box 404, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Brownwood Bulletin on 20th Anniversary of JFK’s Death, 1983 October 5 (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Call Home for Thomas Leath, 1979 November 7 (Box 404, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Cancer Prevention Discussion, 1989 July 28 (Box 404, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Cattle Producers Aid Bill, 1986 May 1 (Box 404, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Central Texas Projects, 1979 July 20 (Box 404, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Challenge on Iran, 1979 November 29 (Box 404, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Civilian Reduction at Fort Hood, 1988 July 12 (Box 404, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Coffee to Honor Leath, 1979 August 10 (Box 404, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Commemoration of Rural Electrification Administration (REA), 1985 May 7 (Box 404, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Community Services Administration (CSA) Grant, 1979 January 19 (Box 404, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Construction Budget Additions, 1989 July 10 (Box 404, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Construction Budget Completion, 1989 October 31 (Box 404, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Continuing Chrysler Expansion in Waco, 1989 January 18 (Box 404, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Copperas Cove Land Exchange, 1988 January 13 (Box 404, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, County Road Improvements, 1979 March 22 (Box 404, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Defense Experts Praise Leath, 1988 November 5 (Box 404, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Defense Project Contracting Out Limit, 1981 April 8 (Box 404, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Department of Defense F-16 NATO Delivery, 1979 January 24 (Box 404, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Department of Education Grant, 1989 January 4 (Box 404, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Designate Texas A&M as a Veteran/Military Services Medical Research University, 1989 August 4 (Box 404, Folder 21)
    - Press Release, Disabled Veterans to Honor Leath, 1982 March 19 (Box 404, Folder 22)
    - Press Release, Disabled-Vet Program Improved, 1979 September 14 (Box 404, Folder 23)
    - Press Release, District Office Staff Travel, 1986 February 1-1986 March 31 (Box 404, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, District Town Meetings, 1987 July 24 (Box 404, Folder 25)
    - Press Release, Douglas Macarthur, 1979 April 27 (Box 404, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, Drug Interdiction Initiative, 1985 February 21 (Box 404, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Economic Development Association (EDA) Grant for San Saba, 1979 January 29 (Box 404, Folder 28)
    - Press Release, Emergency Veterans Job Training Act, 1984 April 10 (Box 404, Folder 29)
    - Press Release, End “Ridiculous” Proposal for VA Regional Office Consolidation, 1985 May 14 (Box 404, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, Equal Status for Traveling Military Dependents, 1983 February 28 (Box 404, Folder 31)
    - Press Release, Essential Air Service Bill, 1989 September 26 (Box 405, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Farm Credit Borrowers Aid, 1986 October 9 (Box 405, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Farm Credit System (FCS) Bill Passes House, 1986 May 21 (Box 405, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Farmers Home Administration Money for Water Supply, 1979 February 23 (Box 405, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Federal Job Information Hotline, 1990 January 4 (Box 405, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Federal Procurement Conference, 1986 August 13 (Box 405, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Federal Spending vs. Pork Barrel Spending, 1979 December 9 (Box 405, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, For 6th Straight Year, Leath Returns Funds to Treasury, 1985 January 15 (Box 405, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, For 8th Straight Year, Leath Returns Funds to Treasury, 1987 February 10 (Box 405, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Construction Project, 1989 February 22 (Box 405, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Funding, 1984 May 9 (Box 405, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Funding, 1985 May 14 (Box 405, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Military Construction, 1985 February 4 (Box 405, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Non-Appropriated Fund Construction Program, 1988 October 13 (Box 405, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Primus Clinics, 1986 September 19 (Box 405, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Statistics, 1984 April 13 (Box 405, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood Study Contracted Out, 1985 October 23 (Box 405, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Fort Hood, TRADOC Combined Arms and Testing Activity (TCATA), 1980 December 19 (Box 405, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Ft. Hood Civilian Personnel Reduction Progress, 1988 April 19 (Box 405, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Ft. Hood-Copperas Cove Land Exchange Finalized, 1988 June 16 (Box 405, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Full Impact Funding, 1979 April 26 (Box 405, Folder 21)
    - Press Release, FY 84 Military Construction Bills, 1983 June 21 (Box 405, Folder 22)
    - Press Release, Gasoline Tax Relief for Farmers, 1980 April 25 (Box 405, Folder 23)
    - Press Release, General, 1981 February 3 (Box 405, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, General, 1980 (Box 405, Folder 25)
    - Press Release, Hearings on Civilian Employee Cuts, 1979 March 16 (Box 405, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, High Score for Leath on Conservative Scorecard, 1979 June 15 (Box 405, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Hood County Courthouse Funds, 1979 January 25 (Box 405, Folder 28)
    - Press Release, House Armed Services Committee Chairmanship, Press Files, 1987 January 2-1987 January 27 (Box 405, Folder 29)
    - Press Release, Impact Aid Testimony, 1989 May 2 (Box 405, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, Include Capital Gains Tax Cut in the Budget Reduction Act, 1989 September 28 (Box 405, Folder 31)
    - Press Release, Increased Trade Between U.S. and Taiwan, 1989 March 23 (Box 405, Folder 32)
    - Press Release, Interior Department Preservation Grant to Bosque County Courthouse, 1979 January 12 (Box 405, Folder 33)
    - Press Release, IRS Tax Code Section 89 Repeal, 1989 September 27 (Box 406, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Issues/Statements (1 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 406, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Issues/Statements (2 of 2), 1983-1984 (Box 406, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Killeen Bicentennial, 1982 May 11 (Box 406, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Killeen School Funding Discussion, 1988 October 19 (Box 406, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Killeen Businessman in White House Conference, 1979 June 4 (Box 406, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Lake Granger Recreation Area Openings, 1981 February 13 (Box 406, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Leath and Stenholm, 1979 August 13 (Box 406, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Leath Announces Retirement, 1989 December 2 (Box 406, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Leath Appointed Chairman of House Panel, 1988 February 4 (Box 406, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Leath Appointed to Defense Policy Panel, 1987 March 11 (Box 406, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Leath Appointed to House Trade and Competitiveness Task Force, 1989 March 22 (Box 406, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Leath Appointed to Two Committees, 1979 January 19 (Box 406, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Leath Assigned to Public Works Subcommittee, 1979 February 1 (Box 407, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Leath Awarded “Guardian of Small Business” by National Federation of Independent Businesses (NFIB), 1982 September 20 (Box 407, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Leath Awarded Small Business Honor, 1984 September 24 (Box 407, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Leath Bill Restricting Contracting Out in VA Hospitals Passed, 1982 July 22 (Box 407, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Leath Blasts Failure of Budget Summit, 1987 November 20 (Box 407, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Leath Budget Chairmanship Decision, 1987 July 27 (Box 407, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Leath Calls for End to Tax Loophole, 1979 March 23 (Box 407, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Leath Calls for Secretary of Agriculture to Step Down, 1979 February 7 (Box 407, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Leath Central Texas Visit, 1982 November 15 (Box 407, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Leath Commends Anti-Drug Bill, 1988 November 1 (Box 407, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Leath Contacts 11th Congressional District Households, 1988 December 16 (Box 407, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Leath Deplores Cuts at VA Medical Facilities, 1979 March 2 (Box 407, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Leath Designated “Taxpayers’ Best Friend”, 1981 May 27 (Box 407, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Leath District Visits, 1983 March 18, 1983 March 24 (Box 407, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Leath Due in San Saba, 1979 August 10 (Box 407, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Leath Elected Chairman of House Budget Task Force on Defense, Foreign Policy, and Space, 1989 February 2 (Box 407, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Leath’s Full Schedule for Texas Trip, 1979 April 9 (Box 407, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Leath’s Full Schedule in Texas, 1979 June 22 (Box 407, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Leath Gets Five Subcommittee Assignments, 1983 January 27 (Box 407, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Leath Hails Passage of Two Veterans Bills, 1981 October 2 (Box 407, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Leath Hails Passage of Two Veterans Bills, 2nd Edition, 1981 October 2 (Box 407, Folder 21)
    - Press Release, Leath Hits Treasury Actions, 1980 March 21 (Box 407, Folder 22)
    - Press Release, Leath Honored by Dairy Farmers, 1989 July 24 (Box 408, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Leath Honored by U.S. Chamber of Commerce, 1989 August 4 (Box 408, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Leath Honored for Efforts to Hold Down Federal Spending, 1984 February 7 (Box 408, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Leath Honored for Peace Through Strength, 1982 March 4 (Box 408, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Leath Honored for Peace Through Strength Efforts, 1983 August 3 (Box 408, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Leath Honored for Support of Federally Impacted Schools, 1990 March 7 (Box 408, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Leath Introduced Legislation to Halt Proposed Office of Management & Budget Revision of VA Hospitals, 1982 April 26 (Box 408, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Leath Introduces Emergency Job Training Bill for Vietnam Veterans, 1983 March 25 (Box 408, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Leath Invited to Accompany Vice President to Arms Talk, 1984 April 11 (Box 408, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Leath Looks Toward 101st Congress, 1988 November 9 (Box 408, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Leath Makes Democratic Response to President’s Radio Message, 1987 August 1 (Box 408, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Leath Meets with Bentsen and Dukakis, 1988 August 5 (Box 408, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Leath Named to 2 Important Armed Services Subcommittees, 1981 January 29 (Box 408, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Leath Named to House/Senate Budget Conference, 1989 May 9 (Box 408, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Leath Named to New Armed Services Committee Panel, 1983 March 25 (Box 408, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Leath Names Assistant for Legislation, Defense, 1980 January 31 (Box 408, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Leath Names Staff in Washington Office, 1979 February 28 (Box 408, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Leath Offers Film on “How Our Laws Are Made”, 1980 July 16 (Box 408, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Leath on President’s Tax Proposal and House Tax Proposal, 1981 July 24 (Box 408, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Leath Opens District Office in Waco, 1979 January 11 (Box 408, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Leath Receives Award (Golden Bulldog), 1984 October 12 (Box 409, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Leath Receives Association of United States Army (AUSA) Award for Distinguished Service, 1984 October 23 (Box 409, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Leath Receives Award for Fiscal Integrity, 1988 September 29 (Box 409, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Leath Receives Award from State Directors of Veterans Affairs, 1984 March 5 (Box 409, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Leath Receives Leadership Award, 1984 April 11 (Box 409, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Leath Receives National Security Leadership Award, 1985 June 4 (Box 409, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Leath Representative toEL, 1980 January-February (Box 409, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Leath Returns Funds to Treasury, 1984 January 11 (Box 409, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Leath Sets Speech in Central Texas, 1979 May 11 (Box 409, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Leath Sponsors Beef Legislation, 1979 January 24 (Box 409, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Explains Media Services, 1979 February 2 (Box 409, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Gatesville & Killeen Visits, 1980 June 13 (Box 409, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff in Belton, Temple on October 8, 1982 October 1 (Box 409, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff in Gatesville, Killeen, 1984 February 15 (Box 409, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff in Meridian, Hamilton, 1984 February 2 (Box 409, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Belton, 1981 October 16 (Box 409, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Belton, Lampasas, 1984 February 22 (Box 409, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Brady, 1981 October 16 (Box 409, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Brownwood, 1984 March 7 (Box 409, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Brownwood, 1983 June 1 (Box 409, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Burnet, 1981 October 21 (Box 409, Folder 21)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Cameron, 1981 October 16 (Box 409, Folder 22)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Gatesville, 1981 October 21 (Box 409, Folder 23)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Gatesville, 1982 September 10 (Box 409, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Glen Rose, 1981 October 31 (Box 409, Folder 25)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Goldthwaite, 1981 October 16 (Box 409, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Granbury, 1981 October 31 (Box 409, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Hamilton, 1981 October 21 (Box 409, Folder 28)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Hamilton, 1982 September 10 (Box 409, Folder 29)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Killeen, 1981 October 9 (Box 409, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Killeen, Florence, 1983 May 18 (Box 409, Folder 31)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Lampasas, 1981 October 9 (Box 409, Folder 32)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Lampasas, 1982 September 10 (Box 409, Folder 33)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Marlin, Goldthwaite, San Saba, Temple, Cameron, Florence, 1984 February 29 (Box 409, Folder 34)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Meridian, 1981 October 2 (Box 409, Folder 35)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Meridian, 1982 September 10 (Box 409, Folder 36)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in San Saba, 1981 October 9 (Box 409, Folder 37)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Taylor, 1981 October 2 (Box 409, Folder 38)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Taylor, 1981 October 9 (Box 409, Folder 39)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Temple, 1981 October 16 (Box 409, Folder 40)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member in Various Towns, 1983 May 4 (Box 409, Folder 41)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Member Travel, 1981 January-February (Box 409, Folder 42)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff to be inEL, 1979 August-September (Box 409, Folder 43)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Visit to Hamilton, Bosque Co., and Burnet, 1980 May 23 (Box 409, Folder 44)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Visits Killeen, San Saba, Goldthwaite, Cameron on September 24, 29, and 30, 1982 September 17 (Box 410, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Visits to Marlin, Brownwood, Florence on September 30, October 1 and 7, 1982 September 24 (Box 410, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Visits to Marlin, Brownwood, Granbury, Brady, and Glen Rose, 1980 June 6 (Box 410, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Leath Staff Visits to San Saba, Taylor, Cameron, Lampasas, Temple, and Belton, 1980 May 30 (Box 410, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Leath Statement for Waco Citizen, 1983 Progress Edition, 1983 June 29 (Box 410, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Leath Tapped for House Armed Services Committee (HASC) Panel on Grace Commission, 1985 March 11 (Box 410, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Leath Tells Amtrak “Good Service or No Support”, 1979 March 30 (Box 410, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Leath Testifies before Agriculture Committee, 1979 February 13 (Box 410, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Leath Testifies on VA Loan Guarantee Bill, 1987 April 22 (Box 410, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Leath to Address Two National Veterans Conventions, 1982 July 9 (Box 410, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Leath to Address Waco Group, 1979 August 10 (Box 410, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Leath to Attend Groundbreaking, 1984 November 6 (Box 410, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Leath to be in Cameron, 1982 January 6 (Box 410, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Leath to be in Hamilton, 1982 January 6 (Box 410, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Leath to be in Lampasas, 1982 January 6 (Box 410, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Leath to be in San Saba, 1982 January 6 (Box 410, Folder 16)
    - Press Release, Leath to Hold Meeting in Cameron, 1982 April 1 (Box 410, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, Leath to Hold Meeting in Hamilton, 1982 April 6 (Box 410, Folder 18)
    - Press Release, Leath to Hold Town Hall Meetings During July Recess, 1980 June 27 (Box 410, Folder 19)
    - Press Release, Leath to Receive American Veterans (AMVETS) Award, 1986 September 22 (Box 410, Folder 20)
    - Press Release, Leath to Seek Re-election, 1986 January 16 (Box 410, Folder 21)
    - Press Release, Leath to Serve on Budget Committee, 1985 January 22 (Box 410, Folder 22)
    - Press Release, Leath to Serve on House Armed Services Committee (HASC), Veterans Affairs Committee, 1983 January 7 (Box 410, Folder 23)
    - Press Release, Leath to Speak in Holland, Killeen, 1979 October 29 (Box 410, Folder 24)
    - Press Release, Leath to Visit in Belton, 1979 August 10 (Box 410, Folder 25)
    - Press Release, Leath to Vote Against Congressional Pay Raise, 1989 February 6 (Box 410, Folder 26)
    - Press Release, Leath Urges Support for Amendment 4, 1981 October 21 (Box 410, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Leath Visit in Gatesville on Thursday, April 23, 1981 April 17 (Box 410, Folder 28)
    - Press Release, Leath Voices Support for Tower, 1989 March 1 (Box 410, Folder 29)
    - Press Release, Leath Will Fight Civilian Reduction at Fort Hood, 1988 March 11 (Box 410, Folder 30)
    - Press Release, Leath Wins Fiscal Responsibility Award, 1980 October 1 (Box 410, Folder 31)
    - Press Release, Leath, Hoffpauir Meeting, 1979 March 9 (Box 410, Folder 32)
    - Press Release, Leath, Wright Head Delegation to Fort Hood, 1980 May 20 (Box 410, Folder 33)
    - Press Release, Leath’s Easter Recess Schedule, 1982 April 1 (Box 410, Folder 34)
    - Press Release, Leath’s Jobs Bill for Veterans Gains Final Approval, 1983 August 2 (Box 410, Folder 35)
    - Press Release, Leath’s Public Appearances, March 27-29, 1982 March 19 (Box 410, Folder 36)
    - Press Release, Leath’s Research Bill Passes U.S. House, 1990 June 12 (Box 410, Folder 37)
    - Press Release, Leath-Anthony Bill Reduces Holding Period for Capital Gains, 1983 March 23 (Box 410, Folder 38)
    - Press Release, Legislation to Curb Bureaucracy, 1979 October 17 (Box 410, Folder 39)
    - Press Release, Legislation to Establish Research Centers, 1990 March 21 (Box 411, Folder 1)
    - Press Release, Mail-order Social Security Organization, 1984 April 4 (Box 411, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Marlin United States Department of Agriculture (USDA) Offices Relocation, 1985 January 8 (Box 411, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Media Correspondence, 1980 (Box 411, Folder 4)
    - Press Release, Medicare Catastrophic Coverage Act Repeal, 1989 October 4 (Box 411, Folder 5)
    - Press Release, Medicare Hospital Payment Protection, 1989 February 24 (Box 411, Folder 6)
    - Press Release, Medicare Recoupment Effort Developments, 1987 November 19 (Box 411, Folder 7)
    - Press Release, Member of Congressional Staff toEL, 1985 February-March (Box 411, Folder 8)
    - Press Release, Member of Congressional Staff toEL, 1987May 18-20 (Box 411, Folder 9)
    - Press Release, Members of Congress Term Limits, 1983 February 18 (Box 411, Folder 10)
    - Press Release, Military Academy Candidates, 1979 December 21 (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - Press Release, Military Dependents User Fees Prohibition, 1989 March 14 (Box 411, Folder 12)
    - Press Release, Military Homeowners Aid Bill, 1985 June 24 (Box 411, Folder 13)
    - Press Release, Military Housing, 1987 February 10 (Box 411, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, Military Refinancing with Veterans Affairs, 1987 March 5 (Box 411, Folder 15)
    - Press Release, Military Renters Bill, 1986 June 7 (Box 411, Folder 16)